greetings everyone this is richard with
hydrogen technology today dot com
uh just real quick video here to show
you a
working ht7 fuel cell hydrogen only
i am separating the gases the uh
fairly complex process i've arrived at
after a year's worth of development
just want to give you a good look at
this um i've got a couple hoses labeled
one that says oxygen the other says
hydrogen of course the hydrogen comes
out
the top the oxygen comes out the side
uh this particular ht7 has been running
for a while in my truck
and i just want to demonstrate for you
now in the next video
the fuel cell running and separating the
gases